A Guide to the Holmes Run Acres Civic Association Collection, 1951-2021
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Activities, 1956-2016
  - Sub-series 3-1: Anniversaries, 1961-2011
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Greetings from HRA - The Time of our Life,” Susan Gaitan, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Little Known Facts,” Vivian Smith, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Our Neighbor, Pioneer Grange,” Vivian Smith, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Stray Thoughts.. .,” Marion-Gray Kraft, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “The Early Settlers,” Martha Powell, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “The Lighter Side”, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Today - As they Dreamed It in Our Past,” Vivian Smith, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Where are the Children”, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication - “Wishes from Children”, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication, Community Service Award, Beth Ann Grove, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Publication, Publication Committee, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HRA 50th Anniversary Holmes Run Acres - The Next 50 Years - Sarah Lahr, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - HRA 60th Anniversary (includes CD with images), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series 3-2: Day in the Park, 1993-2013
    - History of Day in the Park (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Day in the Park flyers, 1993, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Day in the Park, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Day in the Park, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Day in the Park Images (includes original color photographs), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Day in the Park, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Day in the Park, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Day in the Park, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 3-3: House and Garden Tour, 2009-2013
    - HRA Home and Garden Tour, 2009, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - HRA Home and Garden Tour - Color photographs by Jack Underhill, 2011, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - HRA Home and Garden Tour, 2013, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sub-series 3-4: International Dinner, 1999-2011
    - International Dinner Flyer, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - International Dinner and Silent Auction, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - International Dinner and Silent Auction, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - International Dinner and Silent Auction, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - International Dinner and Silent Auction, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - International Dinner and Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - International Dinner, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sub-series 3-5: Oktoberfest, 2014
    - Oktoberfest, 2014, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sub-series 3-6: Open Holmes, 1978-2016
    - Open Holmes - History, 1978-2016 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series 3-7: Various Activities, 1956-2001
    - HRA First Hobby Art Show, 1956 April (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Seventh Annual Area 6 Block Party, 1998 September 12 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Community Yard Sale, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Flowering Tree Planting Project, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Ice Skating Party, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Ice Skating Party, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Ice Skating Party, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Needy Family Christmas Project, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Annual Spring Food and Clothing Drive, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Seventh Annual Food and Clothing Drive, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Series 4: Scrapbooks, Photographs, and Audiovisual Materials, 1950s-2016
  - Sub-series 4-1: Scrapbooks, 1950s-2016
    - Sarah Lahr features on HRA in the Sun Echo newspaper, 1950s [NOTE: In poor physical shape, acidic paper used.] - [MOVED TO BOX 23, SERIES 11: OVERSIZE MATERIALS], 1950s (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - HRA Scrapbook - Compiled by Florence Strickler (Florence was the first historian for HRA) for the 10th Anniversary of HRA, 1961 [NOTE: In poor physical shape, acidic paper used.] - [MOVED TO BOX 24, SERIES 11: OVERSIZE MATERIALS], 1961 (Box 24)
    - HRA Development (from Henry Lowenstern), 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Luria Park (1 of 2), 1954-2012 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Luria Park (2 of 2), 1954-2012 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Hot Topics Through the Years, 1970s-2016 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HRA in the 1980s and 1990s [NOTE: Includes fliers, color photographs and other related materials], 1980-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 4-2: Photographs, 1950s-2002
    - 1950s? - Negatives of Early HRA Houses (Executive Avenue?), 1950s? (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1969 - 3334 Joan Court Party (photos Myrna Guion), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1971 - HRA 20th Anniversary - Negatives of 20th Anniversary HRA Civic Association Celebration, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1980s/1990s - Halloween Parade in Luria Park (includes Negatives), 1980s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1986-1988 - Walnut Hill Estate - became Walnut Hill Patio Homes, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1990 - Open Holmes at Waggoner’s in Olde Towne Alexandria, 1990 Summer (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1991 - 10 Year Awards for Neighborhood Watch, Annandale High School, 1991 Spring (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1991 - Dulin Farm, Site of Providence Park, before the site was developed, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1991 - HRA 40th Anniversary Art Show and Musical Performance, Woodburn Elementary School, 1991 May (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1991 - HRA 40th Anniversary Dinner Celebration (includes Negatives), 1991 May (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1992 - Easter Egg Hunt, 1992 Spring (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 1996 - Negatives of HRA House and Garden Tour (photos Phil Waggoner), 1996 May 4 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1996 - Ethel Theis’ 90th Birthday Party, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1997? - Interviews for Chris Martin Thesis and HRA Publication, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1998 - HRACA Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1999 - HRACA International Dinner, 1999 March 6 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1999 - HRACA Block Host/Hostesses Appreciation Tea at the Gardiner’s House on Hemlock Drive, 1999 September 12 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 2000 - HRA Open Holmes 21st Anniversary Party at Dave and Vivian Smith’s house, 2000 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 2000 - HRACA International Dinner, starting with Cocktail Hour at Barbara Yakovisi’s house and then Dinner at Friendship Methodist Church on Gallows Road, 2000 Winter (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 2000 - HRA Open Holmes at Keith and Haleh Peterson’s home, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 2000 - Fall leaves on Hartwell Ct., 2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 2000? - Painting Luria Park sign at Holmes Run Drive entrance sign, Gary Indre, 2000? (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2001 - House renovations in HRA, 2001 February (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 2001 - Photo Session, First 5-year residents, 2001 Spring (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 2001 - HRA 50th Anniversary, Annual HRACA Meeting (Vivian Smith photos), 2001 May (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 2001 - HRA 50th Anniversary, May Arts Festival (Vivian Smith photos), Day in the Park, Holmes Run Acres Garden Tour, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 2001 - HRA 50th Anniversary Spring Park Clean Up (photos Scott Birkhead), 2001 Fall (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 2001 - HRA 50th Anniversary House Tour (photos Vivian Smith and Phil Waggoner), 2001 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 2001- HRA 50th Anniversary Gala (photos by Vivian Smith, Phil Waggoner, and Bob Shipp; Mia Gardiner from cameras put on tables; and from poster board display at HRACA 50th Anniversary Gala) (1 of 2), 2001 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 2001- HRA 50th Anniversary Gala (photos by Vivian Smith, Phil Waggoner, and Bob Shipp; Mia Gardiner from cameras put on tables; and from poster board display at HRACA 50th Anniversary Gala) [includes seating chart] (2 of 2), 2001 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 2001 - HRA 50th Anniversary Day in the Park (photos Bobb Shipp & Phil Waggoner), 2001 October 7 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 2002? - Block Party - Sherwood Court, 2002 September 1? (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 2002? - Candlelight Vigil, organized by Alia Badi’s, 2002 September 18? (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 2002 - Welcome Picnic, Marian and Little John Courts - to welcome the Rupps, Danius and Yoshiko Bardzukas (Aryvdas Bardzukas’ nephew) and the Mallet/Clines to HRA, 2002 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Photos - HRA residents, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - HRA - The Early Years - Photos on Posterboard, photos by Florence Strickler [MOVED TO BOX 23, SERIES 11: OVERSIZE MATERIALS], 1961 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sub-series 4-3: Videotapes (VHS), 2001
    - HRA Arts Festival and Garden Tour May 16, 2001; HRA House Tour, October 6, 2001; HRA Day in the Park, October 8, 2001 (Unedited version, Terry Barcus), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Vivian Smith - Brief Interview; Marriott Dinner; Annual Meeting at Woodburn Elementary School, 2001 (HRA 50th anniversary) (Unedited version, by Terry Barcus), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series 4-4: Audiocassettes, 1971
    - HRA 20th anniversary - Recording of entertainment (includes recording notes), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 4-5: Compact Discs (CDs), 2001-2012
    - 1951-2001 Holmes Run Acres 50th Anniversary Celebration (includes CD-ROM), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - A Celebration of the life of Sarah Lahr (photos by Paul Fetters), 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Special Interest/Subject Files, 1952-2018
  - Holmes Runner - History and Early Manuals, 1950s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - “A Look Back in Time” House and Garden Tours over the last 44 years, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - HRA Anniversary Celebrations (1 of 2) (includes photos), 1976-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - HRA Anniversary Celebrations (2 of 2) (includes photos), 1976-1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Luria Park (includes photos), 1961-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Changing Times - Clippings, 1960s-2011 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - HRA brochures, fliers, notices and forms, 1981-2011 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Home and Garden Tours, 1967-2011 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Potpourri of The Holmes Runner Covers (1 of 2), 1952-2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Potpourri of The Holmes Runner Covers (2 of 2), 1952-2008 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The “McMansion” Phenomenon, Housing boom days, 2000-2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Grange - (Annandale/Masonville Rds.) - Photos: Historical changes, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Project - HRA CD-ROM (includes CD-ROM), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Collected Gardening Notes, 1961-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Holmes Runner - Notes on contents, 1953-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Community activities and interests over the years, 1973-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - HRA Revitalization Program, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - “Tract-House Modern: A Study of Housing Design and Consumption in the Washington Suburbs, 1946-1960" - Christopher T. Martin, PhD thesis - Former HRA resident, chapters that concern HRA (1 of 2), 2000 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - “Tract-House Modern: A Study of Housing Design and Consumption in the Washington Suburbs, 1946-1960" - Christopher T. Martin, PhD thesis - Former HRA resident, chapters that concern HRA (2 of 2), 2000 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Community Survey - Final Report, 1998 April (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Luria Park - Fairfax County Park Authority, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Woodburn School, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - History poster items, 2002, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Snomageddon, 2011 January 28 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Annandale Chamber of Commerce - Community Directory, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Washington Post classifieds - Examples of types of women’s jobs, 1963, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearing information - Fairfax County - Gallows Rd. And Rt. 50 interchange, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous community concerns over the years, 1952-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - HRA - Traffic, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - HRA - Brightview development, 2012-2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Gallows Road - Flashing crosswalk - Sarah Karush, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Speed Abatement - HRA neighborhood signs, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - HRA residents and associated people - Passed away, 2012, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - HRA - Development - General, 2010-2018 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - List of HRA artists and crafts people, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Capital Beltway widening, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - A few items arranged by early decades (see HRA History, volume III for Susan Gaitan’s chronology by decades), 1951-2011 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series 6: Holmes Run Acres Recreation Association (otherwise known as the Holmes Run Pool), 1955-2014
  - Certificate of Incorporation and Bylaws - HRARA, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - HRACA and HRARA Ad Hoc Committee Understanding, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Image - Pool Board at the time of incorporation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - “The Big Splash and Ten Years of Fun in the Sun, 1953-1963: A History of Our Pool” - Florence Strickler, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Standard Procedures, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Photographs and Negatives, 1965-1966, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1965, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1968, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1969, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1974, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1977, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1978, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 1979, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 1982, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 1983, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1984, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1985, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1986, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1987 - Includes photographs, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1988, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1996, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1997, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1998, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1999, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 2000, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2001, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2002, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2003, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2004 - Cell Tower, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2005, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2007, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Pool Memories, 1955-1963, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Series 7: National Register of Historic Places, 2002-2007
  - Exploration of HRA being on the National Register of Historic Places (1 of 2) [Note: Includes the Gray & Pape, Inc. - Cultural Resources Consultants’ - “An Architectural Evaluation of the Proposed Holmes Run Acres Historic District for the Capital Beltway (Route 495) Project, March 18, 2002”], 2002-2007 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Exploration of HRA being on the National Register of Historic Places (2 of 2), 2002-2007 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Citizens Guide to Section 106 Review, p. 8 for consultant parties Protecting Historic Properties, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - HRA National Historic Registry - Nomination and Acceptance Correspondence (including electronic versions: 3.5” floppy disk, 2 CDs), 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Historic District Boundary Maps, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - EHT Traceries - Reconnaissance Level Survey, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0001-0035, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0036-0070, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0071-0106, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0107-0142, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0143-0177, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0178-0213, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0214-0249, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0250-0285, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Survey, Field Form 0286-0338, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0001-0030, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0031-0060, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0061-0090, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0091-0120, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0121-0150, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0151-0180, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0181-0210, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0211-0240, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0241-0270, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0271-0300, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0301-0330, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Department of Historic Resources - Reconnaissance Level Survey - Eligibility status, 0331-0338, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - HRA Architectural Surveys, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - HRA National Register of Historic Places Plaque Program, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - HRA - Historic plaque order form, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Series 8: Publications, 1952-2012
  - Series 8-1: The Holmes Runner, 1952-2012
    - The Holmes Runner - Editors, 1952-2001, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - The Holmes Runner - “Peanuts” issue, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Holmes Runner - Administrative, 2001-2009 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Holmes Runner - Editorial oversight, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Holmes Runner - List of Articles, 1983-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - The Holmes Runner - Christmas card from the Runner staff, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - The Holmes Runner [NOTE: Two copies of the first issue, includes editor’s files], 1952 August (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Holmes Runner, 1952 September (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The Holmes Runner, 1952 October (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - The Holmes Runner, 4th issue (2 copies), 1952 November (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - The Holmes Runner, the Mad Magazine Issue, 1961 June (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - The Holmes Runner, First one by photocopier (Xerox), 1981 April (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - The Holmes Runner, 30 Years 1953-1983, 1983 January/February (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - The Holmes Runner, 40th Anniversary Issue - 2 copies with one containing notes from Vivian Smith, HRA Historian, 1991 May (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - The Holmes Runner, 50th Anniversary Celebration 1951-2001, 2001 Fall (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - The Holmes Runner, Happy 50th Anniversary Year 1951-2001, 2001 Winter (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Holmes Runner, Celebration 50 Years of Community News, 2002 Autumn (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Holmes Runner, Holiday 2006, Happy 55th HRA!, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - The Holmes Runner, Celebrating 60 Years, 2011 Summer (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - The Holmes Runner, Celebrating 60 Years in Print 1952-2012, 2012 Fall (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Series 8-2: General Publications, 1961-2011
    - Mrs. Wheat’s Own Coloring Book (Blanche Wheat was Woodburn Elementary School’s first principal), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Articles from The Holmes Runner by Sarah Lahr: The Community Within and Beyond, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - HRA Cookbook, probably for 10th HRA anniversary (2 copies), c. 1961 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Cookbook, 1991 40th Anniversary HRA - File Copy, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Holmes Run Acres: The Story of a Community, Volume I - File Copy, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Holmes Run Acres: The Story of a Community, Volume II - File Copy, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Holmes Run Acres: The Story of a Community, Volume III - File Copy, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Report by the HRACA Survey Committee to the HRACA Board, 1998 April (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HRA Publications Price List - 50th Anniversary, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Nature in Our Acres - 50th Anniversary, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Poetry, Holmes Run Acres, 1951-2011, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Art in the Acres: HRA Cartoons and Illustrations, 1952-2011, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Yarding About with the Graine Thumb in Holmes Run Acres - 50th Anniversary, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Series 9: Directories, 1954-2021
  - Directories - Items of note by Vivian Smith, Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 2, 1954 January (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 3, 1954 November (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 4, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 5, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 6, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 7, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 8, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 9, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 10, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 11, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 12, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 13, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, Number 14, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Holmes Run Acres Directory, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)